{
    "subject": "Frederick_III_of_Denmark",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sophie_Amalie_of_Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg",
    "human_readable": "Frederick III of Denmark is married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887508749961853,
            "question": "Who were the spouses of Frederick III of Denmark and Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.979704737663269,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Frederick III of Denmark and Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9764542579650879,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Frederick III of Denmark and Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9635049104690552,
            "question": "To whom was Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9631510972976685,
            "question": "Who was Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534667134284973,
            "question": "Who was Frederick III of Denmark married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534225463867188,
            "question": "Was Frederick III of Denmark married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204017519950867,
            "question": "Can you name a monarch who was married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903716206550598,
            "question": "What was the name of Frederick III of Denmark's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708900213241577,
            "question": "What is the name of Frederick III of Denmark's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick III of Denmark is married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg.",
            "html": "yago_2161_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Frederick III of Denmark's wife?",
            "html": "yago_2161_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a monarch who was married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg?",
            "html": "yago_2161_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Frederick III of Denmark married?",
            "html": "yago_2161_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2161_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided confirm that Frederick III of Denmark was indeed married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg. This information can be found in multiple files, such as `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2161/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2161/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that supports the statement \"Frederick III of Denmark is married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg.\" Specifically, the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2161/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt` mentions that Frederick III of Denmark was previously married to Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg from 1643 to 1670, and the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2161/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt` confirms that they were married for 26 years. Additionally, the birth of their children is documented in another file, further confirming this relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}